This
-—-—-
It island
If there is no one who brows with the horn layer ...
Here comes the winter
Oohh I'm so thirsty
Where is there water, where is there water
And then it starts looking.
Uhrrrr
Well then we would collapse like empty bags.
Now it is
Hack chop
Hack chop chop
chop chop chop chopping
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
The whole house is full of childhood diseases.
But one must not itch
No
And then I recommend
that you only eat
Mashed food.
(mm mums)
Starts all the antibodies to go
in a scarlet fever school.
Cold...
Hello
Cold.
Now check out all these yellow pups.
We say I poke myself in the eye.
Remember that this is a yellow plump.
But now
Now the body gets angry
Minisnort
MM :)
Thanks Eva
Yes please.
You can get hnh
Snake many times.
The immune system
Hoh!
& gt ;: D
Banking Banka row.
Knock bank bank bank bank bank
And knock knocking knocks!
Namen what happened here now: o
Yes, hay hay, these they can't very much.
(a bit like me: '))
Hoh: o
He recognizes this one
I'm thinking of my mind
Mash Mosa Mosa
Mash Mosa Mash Mosa Mash Mosa
Mash mosa mosa mosa mosa mosa mosa mosa mosa mosa
Mash mosa mosa mash mosa mo
Bllölörp
and if you laugh too little
Blööschh
fart
Ahh hahah!
You want to swim on Saturdays,
You want to go on a party
Tuuut
yeah
to take it easy
And just look at clouds.
Hmmm :)
And then another thing.
Eat with cutlery.
Now I will sneeze
Atcho
hm
Why do you have to sleep for (I am a borch literally this at 05:03 i'm Sorry Eva I have failed you)
And the toes they can actually spin on like this.
Let your hands fall oouu
Häjsaan
Fruit and green poop nice!
AA:/
It will be showering.
Yes it continues here.
Bajs rally continues ️
The journey in the small intestine is over.
looks like this.
Hehehaah
Yes and here it lay down and stumbles a little neighbor and
Petting a little on one
Pliing
Now we have fixed a real constipation (yaaay good job!)
Ooouup
Aaah lovely!
Check
So down in the large intestine
Näää :(